Makaruos mekhail yousab

Frontend Angular Developer

makaruosmekhail@gmail.com 📞 01090342871 👂 Ramsess, cario

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/makaruos-mekhail-144862257/ 🐧 https://github.com/makaruos-mekhail

https://portofolio-makaruos.vercel.app/

PROFILE

I am a software engineer specializing in designing and developing websites using Angular. I am extremely passionate about the field of programming and web design. My goal is to gain as much knowledge and experience as possible, while enhancing my skills in design and programming to the highest level. I thoroughly enjoy the process of developing and learning new technologies and skills in the future.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Angular Developer | Full-Time

10/2023 – present | New Cairo, Egypt

Uktra Digital Solutions

- Developed 10+ web applications using Angular, TypeScript, and UI frameworks including Bootstrap, SCSS, and PrimeNG , talwiend css , and Restfull API.
- Designed and implemented exceptional, responsive UIs with smooth animation scroll page, using Figma, SCSS, and PrimeNG components.
- Experienced in e-commerce development, leveraging Bootstrap for responsive layouts and PrimeNG components for rich user interactions.
- Maintains professional project architecture that effectively integrates Angular, TypeScript, and various UI frameworks.
- Furthermore, I implement permission and authentication systems to ensure restricted access to specific pages based on

Freelancer project | part time (Sham-Pistachio)

02/2024 - 04/2024 | cario

Freelancer

The Pistachio-Sham Project is an online store focused on Pistachio Al Sham confectionery and nuts shops. It aims to showcase their products, menus, special offers, and provide means of communication with them.

Technologies used in the project include Angular, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Sass, KeenSlider, multi-language support, Reactive Forms, and RESTful APIs.



EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Using .Net

12/2022 - 04/2023

Information Technology Institute (ITI)

I participated in a Full Stack Web Development program focused on the .Net & Angular stack. The internship provided me with hands-on experience and knowledge in various web tools and technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, as well as frontend platforms like Angular, and backend technologies such as asp.net.

Software Engineering Fundamentals

07/2022 - 12/2022

Information Technology Institute (ITI)

I actively participated in a comprehensive Software Engineering Fundamentals program. This program provided a strong foundation in (C, C++), data structures, and web development (HTML, CSS, WordPress), I gained exposure to WordPress, equipping me with the skills to create and manage websites.

Computer Information System

09/2018 - 06/2022

Cairo University

• Graduation Grade: Very Good (C+)



SKILLS

Angular | TypeScript | JavaScript | ES6 | HTML5 & Css3 | Sass | Animation scroll page | Restfull API | Bootstrap | Primeng | ReactiveForm | Responsive Web Design | WordPress | SQL Server | Git | GitHub | Data Structure | asp.net | C# | C++

Use Figma Ui&Ux - Permission & Authentication page | Scan Qr Code | talwiend css

Use cPanl provides the server and site management platform

Soft Skills (Problem Solving | Teamwork | Self-Learning | Research Skills)



Training In The C# Programming Language

My Certificate

Technologies: (C# Console Application – C# Form Application – C# OOP)

Course Training In The Database

10/2020 - 02/2021 | Nasr City, cairo

10/2020 - 02/2021 | Nasr City, cairo

My Certificate

Technologies: (Microsoft Access – SQL Server Manegment – SQL Server Code)



PROJECTS

Projects (Uktra Company)

Technologies: Using Angular frameworks | TypeScript | HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap | Sass | Animation scroll page | Permission & Authentication page | Scan Qr Code | talwiend css | Responsive Web Design | KeenSlider | multi language | Reactive Form | Restfull API.

Hani george (Uktra) 🔗

The Hany-George Project is dedicated to Hany George's modern lighting and columns stores. It entails a website for the company showcasing its details, products, brands, latest news, team work, and communication channels.

K-Group ∂

This project, owned by K-Group, serves as the company's official website. It is dedicated to showcasing the company's products and providing detailed information about its offerings.

Origin (Uktra) 🔗

The Origin Project involves developing a website for the company to showcase its details, products, brands, latest news, team, and communication channels.

Deoss Congress \mathscr{D}

This project is for the Deoss Congress World Eye Symposium, announcing and detailing the event featuring renowned ophthalmologists and eye disease specialists.

Fanarah Schools (Uktra) 🔗

The Project is focused on Fanarah Language Schools, offering an online platform for students' applications through a form submission. The website provides comprehensive details about the school.

Prints(Uktra) &

The Prints Project is dedicated to providing a website for printing orders in all forms, including invitations, cards, and more. It offers details about the services, facilitates online ordering, and features essential functions such as login, sign up, cart management, checkout, and custom design options. Additionally, it ensures seamless communication channels.

Portfolio-me &

Technologies: Using Angular | HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap | Sass | Darkmode | multi language | Reactive Form | TypeScript | Animation scroll page | KeenSlider .

Noon Clone Graduation Project ITI Angular 🔗

Technologies: Using Angular | Restfull API | HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap5 | MySQL | Typescript | payment PayPal | Reactive Form & Lazy loading .

Amazon Clone Frontend HTML5 & Css3 & JS 🔗

Technologies: Using HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap5.3 | JavaScript | ES6.

Noon Clone Frontend HTML5 & Css3 & JS ⊘

Technologies: Using HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap5.3 | JavaScript | ES6.

1	€	h
	u	,

LANGUAGES

Arabic	English
Native	Good